const questions=[
    {
        no: "1",
        question: "You're 3rd place right now in a race. What place are you in when you pass the person in 2nd place?",
        A: "1st",
        B: "2nd",
        C: "3rd",
        D: "None of the above.",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "2",
        question: "How many months have 28 days?",
        A: "2",
        B: "1",
        C: "All of them.",
        D: "Depends if there's a leap year or not.",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        no: "3",
        question: "How many 0.5cm slices of bread can you cut from a whole bread that's 25cm long? ",
        A: "1",
        B: "25",
        C: "39",
        D: "None of the above.",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "4",
        question: "The answer is really big.",
        A: "THE ANSWER.",
        B: "Really big.",
        C: "An elephant.",
        D: "The data given is insufficient.",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "5",
        question: "Divide 30 by half and add ten. ",
        A: "40.5",
        B: "30",
        C: "70",
        D: "I know this is a trick question, so NONE. Ha!",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        no: "6",
        question: "There are two clocks of different colors: The red clock is broken and doesn't run at all, but the blue clock loses one second every 24 hours. Which clock is more accurate? ",
        A: "The red clock.",
        B: "The blue clock.",
        C: "Neither.",
        D: "Both.",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "7",
        question: "A farmer has 17 sheep, all of them but 8 die. How many sheep are still standing? ",
        A: "8",
        B: "9",
        C: "25",
        D: "35",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "8",
        question: "If a leaf falls to the ground in a forest and no one hears it, does it make a sound?",
        A: "Yes",
        B: "No",
        C: "Depends on how heavy the leaf was.",
        D: "Depends on where it landed.",
        answer: "A",
      },
      {
        no: "9",
        question: "There are 45 apples in your basket. You take three apples out of the basket. How many apples are left?",
        A: "3",
        B: "42",
        C: "45",
        D: "I do not eat apple!",
        answer: "C",
      },
      {
        no: "10",
        question: "Mathew's father has three sons- Joseph I and Joseph II. Can you guess the name of the third son?",
        A: "Joseph III",
        B: "Jerin",
        C: "Mathew",
        D: "jenir",
        answer: "A",
      },

];
module.exports=questions;